Gavin Hung 7488 Tiptoe Lane Cupertino, CA 95014

June 8th, 2020

A4 Bootcamp 450 Serra Mall Stanford, CA 94305

Dear A4 Team,

I am writing in regard to the A4 Machine Learning Internship. I believe that my past experiences in utilizing machine learning, teaching programming, and working as a software team lead make me a good fit for the position.

First, I have used my machine learning skills to create useful applications. In a past hackathon, my team and I created an IOS app that can detect sign language gestures from the user in real time. We trained convolutional neural networks to find hands and classify the sign language character. I have also been learning TensorFlow to create recurrent and convolutional neural networks that can predict data and classify images. I have experience working with Google Colab to write Jupyter Notebooks.

Second, I have independently ran Python and Java coding camps. I developed the curriculum to suit students with varying degrees of experience in coding. When designing coding exercises for the class, I thought about the challenges I faced when I was a beginner programmer and made sure to address the roadblocks I encountered. I enjoy mentoring students and challenging them to approach problems from different perspectives.

Lastly, as a software lead on the school robotics team, I have experience managing a team and overseeing the coding of the robot. I maintain great communication between the hardware and electrical divisions to ensure that deadlines are met before competitions.

I do not have any major commitments until late August and am available to work immediately both in-person in the Bay Area and remotely. I would like to use my skills to help create an educational and fulfilling boot camp for students at A4. Please contact me at 408-674-8660 or at gavinkhung@gmail.com, if you have any further questions. Thank you for your consideration.

Sincerely, Gavin Hung

Gavin Hung

gavinkhung@gmail.com • (408) 674-8660

Education

Monta Vista High School

Rising Junior, GPA 4.0/4.0

Cupertino, California Expected Graduation in 2022

Technical Skills

Languages: Python, JavaScript, Java, Shell, Dart, HTML, CSS

Frameworks and Libraries: Node, React, Flutter, Tensorflow, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Flask, Docker

Applications: Microsoft Office, Google Suite, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator

Relevant Experience

Monta Vista Robotics Club

Cupertino, California August 2019 - Present

Software Lead

• Led a group of 5 students to develop code that served as the brain/logic of the robot.

- Created the algorithm that uses computer vision to find targets and auto-align the robot to face the target.
- Programmed the LED lights around the robot and the conveyor belt system.
- Taught at the Head-Start program for 50 hrs to introduce incoming freshmen to how to code a robot.

Hongyun Art

Cupertino, California

Summer 2019

Computer Science Python Teacher

- Engaged with students in groups and individually to help them apply coding concepts in the Tkinter python library to create artistic applications.
- Taught the fundamentals of programming and the syntax of python.
- Gained experience teaching and communicating complex concepts to students with little to no coding experience.

Green Apple Education Java & Python Teacher

Cupertino, California Winter 2017, Spring 2018

- Independently ran a coding camp for 3-5 students from a range of coding backgrounds.
- Developed a syllabus and curriculum for teaching the fundamentals of both Java and Python, including loops, variables, inputs, arrays, control flow, algorithms, functions, logical operators, and if-else statements.
- Guided students through in-class lab coding assignments and prepared instructional materials for labs.

Hackathons/Projects

• Jai Krishi: (In Development Phase)

May 2020-Present

- Creating an IOS/Android app for farmers to detect crop diseases from images/weather data using Fastai & Flutter.
- Sigma Hacks: IOS app to help people with visual impairment

Nov 2019

- Used ML to identify items depicted in video captured by the user in real-time.
- Used augmented reality to calculate the distance between objects and displayed information to the user.
- Omni Hacks 1st Place: IOS app with Swift that used ML to classify sign language gestures

Sept 2019

- Used two convoluted neural networks using TensorFlow and CoreML.

Extracurriculars

• Staff Writer: Responsible for multi-media aspects of the El Estoque Student Newspaper May 2020–Present

Staff Writer: Researched topics, interviewed teachers, and wrote articles for Res Novae Newspaper Sept 2019–Present

• Website Master: Maintained and updated the Monta Vista Robotics Team website

Aug 2019-Present

• Co-founder: Co-Founded Gen Z Times Podcast, discussing new tech advancements

Jun 2019-Present

• Mentor: Mentored Pixel Hacks hackathon participants and provided guidance on troubleshooting code

Feb 2020

Pixel Hacks IV is an all-female high school hackathon that promotes women in STEM.
Museum Interpreter: Volunteered at the Tech Interactive Museum for 115 hrs

Nov 2018-Dec 2019

- Ran labs and communicated technical concepts in cybersecurity, robotics, and physics to museum visitors.

Leadership

• *Director of Technology* for the Monta Vista TedX Club

May 2020–Present

• Secretary for the Monta Vista Astronomy and Astrophysics Club

May 2020-Present

• *Director of Technology* for Byte Hacks Online Hackathon

Nov 2019-Present